A Guide to the Barksdale Theatre Records 1945-2006 (bulk 1954-2004)
Library of Virginia
- Series V. Newspaper clippings and newsletters, 1953-2002., Extent: 3.5 cu. ft. (10 boxes). (Box 18-27)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Rainmaker 1956 (Box-folder 21:13)
  - Clippings, Productions, To Rise One Day 1957 (Box-folder 21:14)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Lady's Not for Burning 1957 (Box-folder 21:15)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Little Hut 1957 (Box-folder 21:16)
  - Clippings, Productions, Portrait in Black 1957 (Box-folder 21:17)
  - Clippings, Productions, Dirty Work at the Crossroads 1957 (Box-folder 21:18)
  - Clippings, Productions, Amphitryon 38 1957 (Box-folder 21:19)
  - Clippings, Productions, Arsenic and Old Lace 1958 (Box-folder 21:20)
  - Clippings, Productions, Matchmaker 1958 (Box-folder 21:21)
  - Clippings, Productions, 1958 (Box-folder 21:22)
  - Clippings, Productions, Where's Charley? 1959 (Box-folder 21:23)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Crucible 1959 (Box-folder 21:24)
  - Clippings, Productions, A Streetcar named desire 1960 (Box-folder 21:25)
  - Clippings, Productions, Private Lives 1960 (Box-folder 21:25a)
  - Clippings, Productions, Picnic 1960 (Box-folder 21:26)
  - Clippings, Productions, Mr. Roberts 1961 (Box-folder 21:27)
  - Clippings, Productions, Critic's Choice (Box-folder 21:28)
  - The Fantasticks 1963 (Box-folder 21:29)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Boyfriend 1964 (Box-folder 21:30)
  - Clippings, Productions, Lullaby 1965 (Box-folder 21:31)
  - Clippings, Productions, Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf? 1966-1967 (Box-folder 21:32)
  - Clippings, Productions, Luv 1967 (Box-folder 21:33)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Champagne Complex 1967 (Box-folder 21:34)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Patriots 1973 (Box-folder 21:35)
  - Clippings, Productions, You Can't Take it With You 1974-1976 (Box-folder 21:36)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Front Page 1974 (Box-folder 21:37)
  - Clippings, Productions, Godspell 1975 (Box-folder 22:1)
  - Clippings, Productions, Ah, Wilderness 1975 (Box-folder 22:2)
  - Clippings, Productions, UTBU 1976 (Box-folder 22:3)
  - Clippings, Productions, Rosencrantz and Guildenstern 1976 (Box-folder 22:4)
  - Clippings, Productions, I Never Sang for My Father 1976 (Box-folder 22:5)
  - Clippings, Productions, Ladies in Retirement 1976 (Box-folder 22:6)
  - Clippings, Productions, Any Given Wednesday 1977 (Box-folder 22:7)
  - Clippings, Productions, Red, Hot, and Cole 1977-1979 (Box-folder 22:8)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Little Hut 1978 (Box-folder 22:9)
  - Clippings, Productions, Equus 1978 (Box-folder 22:10)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Royal Family 1978 (Box-folder 22:11)
  - Clippings, Productions, Man of La Mancha 1978 (Box-folder 22:12)
  - Clippings, Productions, Red, Hot, and Cole (Touring, Los Angeles, CA) 1979 (Box-folder 22:13)
  - Clippings, Productions, One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest 1979 (Box-folder 22:14)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Importance of Being Earnest 1979 (Box-folder 22:15)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Man Who Came To Dinner 1979 (Box-folder 22:16)
  - Clippings, Productions, Old Wives Tale 1979 (Box-folder 22:17)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Good Doctor 1979 (Box-folder 22:18)
  - Clippings, Productions, Chapter Two 1980 (Box-folder 22:19)
  - Clippings, Productions, Da 1980 (Box-folder 22:20)
  - Clippings, Productions, Murder at Howard Johnson's 1980 (Box-folder 22:21)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Mikado 1980 (Box-folder 22:22)
  - Clippings, Productions, Light Up the Sky 1980 (Box-folder 22:23)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Elephant Man 1980 (Box-folder 22:24)
  - Clippings, Productions, HMS Pinafore 1981 (Box-folder 22:25)
  - Clippings, Productions, 1940's Radio Hour 1981 (Box-folder 22:26)
  - Clippings, Productions, Gertrude Stein, Gertrude Stein 1982 (Box-folder 22:27)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Pirates of Penzance 1982 (Box-folder 22:28)
  - Clippings, Productions, Sweeney Todd 1982-1983 (Box-folder 22:29)
  - Clippings, Productions, What the Butler Saw 1983 (Box-folder 22:30)
  - Clippings, Productions, George Washington Slept Here 1983 (Box-folder 22:31)
  - Clippings, Productions, Patience 1983 (Box-folder 22:32)
  - Clippings, Productions, A Couple of White Chicks Sitting Around 1983 (Box-folder 22:33)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Middle Ages 1983 (Box-folder 22:34)
  - Clippings, Productions, Talking With... 1984 (Box-folder 23:1)
  - Clippings, Productions, Present Laughter 1984 (Box-folder 23:2)
  - Clippings, Productions, Foxfire 1984 (Box-folder 23:3)
  - Clippings, Productions, Here's A How-De-Do 1984 (Box-folder 23:4)
  - Clippings, Productions, Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat 1985-1986 (Box-folder 23:5)
  - Clippings, Productions, Taking my Turn 1986 (Box-folder 23:6)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Circle 1986 (Box-folder 23:7)
  - Clippings, Productions, Brighton Beach Memoirs 1986 (Box-folder 23:8)
  - Clippings, Productions, Mornings at Seven 1986 (Box-folder 23:9)
  - Clippings, Productions, Vanities 1987 (Box-folder 23:10)
  - Clippings, Productions, Butterfingers Angel, Mary & Joseph, Herod the Nut, & the Slaughter of 12 Hit Carols in a Pear Tree 1987 (Box-folder 23:11)
  - Clippings, Productions, Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat (Touring show) 1987 (Box-folder 23:12)
  - Clippings, Productions, Tallulah-A Memory 1987 (Box-folder 23:13)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Amorous Flea 1987 (Box-folder 23:14)
  - Clippings, Productions, Artichoke 1988 (Box-folder 23:15)
  - Clippings, Productions, Nunsense 1988-1995 (Box-folder 23:16)
  - Clippings, Productions, Hot Grog 1988 (Box-folder 23:17)
  - Clippings, Productions, A Child's Christmas in Wales 1988 (Box-folder 23:18)
  - Clippings, Productions, Painting Churches 1988 (Box-folder 23:19)
  - Clippings, Productions, One West Main 1989 (Box-folder 23:20)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Mikado 1989 (Box-folder 23:21)
  - Clippings, Productions, You Can Never Tell 1989 (Box-folder 23:22)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Nerd 1989 (Box-folder 23:23)
  - Clippings, Productions, Wenceslaus Square 1989 (Box-folder 23:24)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Land of Fire 1990 (Box-folder 23:25)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Cocktail Hour 1990 (Box-folder 23:26)
  - Clippings, Productions, Earnest in Love 1990 (Box-folder 23:27)
  - Clippings, Productions, A Trip to Bountiful 1990 (Box-folder 24:1)
  - Clippings, Productions, Steppin' Out 1990 (Box-folder 24:2)
  - Clippings, Productions, On the Verge 1990 (Box-folder 24:3)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Loves of Cass McGuire 1991 (Box-folder 24:4)
  - Clippings, Productions, Home Games 1991 (Box-folder 24:5)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Zulu and the Zayda 1991 (Box-folder 24:6)
  - Clippings, Productions, Oh, Coward 1991 (Box-folder 24:7)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Lady's Not for Burning 1991 (Box-folder 24:8)
  - Clippings, Productions, Oil City Symphony 1991 (Box-folder 24:9)
  - Clippings, Productions, Lucky Stiff 1992 (Box-folder 24:10)
  - Clippings, Productions, A Christmas Carol 1992 (Box-folder 24:11)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Road to Mecca 1992 (Box-folder 24:12)
  - Clippings, Productions, Social Security 1992 (Box-folder 24:13)
  - Clippings, Productions, Tender Lies 1992 (Box-folder 24:14)
  - Clippings, Productions, American Beauty 1992 (Box-folder 24:15)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Voice of the Turtle 1993 (Box-folder 25:1)
  - Clippings, Productions, The 40th Year Gala 1993 (Box-folder 25:2)
  - Clippings, Productions, By Strouse 1993 (Box-folder 25:3)
  - Clippings, Productions, Death of a Salesman 1993 (Box-folder 25:4)
  - Clippings, Productions, Bojangles 1993 (Box-folder 25:5)
  - Clippings, Productions, Oh Dad, Poor Dad 1993 (Box-folder 25:6)
  - Clippings, Productions, Godspell 1993 (Box-folder 25:7)
  - Clippings, Productions, Talley's Folly 1994 (Box-folder 25:8)
  - Clippings, Productions, The World Goes Round 1994 (Box-folder 25:9)
  - Clippings, Productions, A Day in Hollywood/A Night in the Ukraine 1994 (Box-folder 25:10)
  - Clippings, Productions, Love Letters 1994 (Box-folder 25:11)
  - Clippings, Productions, Our Town 1994 (Box-folder 25:12)
  - Clippings, Productions, Falsetto's 1994 (Box-folder 25:13)
  - Clippings, Productions, Zelda the Last Flapper 1994 (Box-folder 25:14)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Turn of the Screw 1994 (Box-folder 25:15)
  - Clippings, Productions, Oleanna 1995 (Box-folder 25:16)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Glass Menagerie 1995 (Box-folder 25:17)
  - Clippings, Productions, Born Yesterday 1995 (Box-folder 25:18)
  - Clippings, Productions, Once on This Island 1995 (Box-folder 25:19)
  - Clippings, Productions, Prelude to a Kiss 1995 (Box-folder 25:20)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Taffetas 1996 (Box-folder 25:21)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Search for Signs of Intelligent Life 1996 (Box-folder 25:22)
  - Clippings, Productions, Love, Valour, Compassion 1997 (Box-folder 25:23)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Hosue of Blue Leaves 1997 (Box-folder 25:24)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Woman in Black 1997 (Box-folder 25:25)
  - Clippings, Productions, Red, Hot, and Cole 1997 (Box-folder 25:26)
  - Clippings, Productions, Molly Sweeney 1997 (Box-folder 25:27)
  - Clippings, Productions, Blues in the Night 1997 (Box-folder 25:28)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Complete Wks of Wllm Shkspr 1997 (Box-folder 25:29)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Young Man from Atlanta 1997 (Box-folder 25:30)
  - Clippings, Productions, She Loves Me 1998 (Box-folder 25:31)
  - Clippings, Productions, From the Mississippi Delta 1998 (Box-folder 25:32)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Rocky Horror Picture Show 1998 (Box-folder 25:33)
  - Clippings, Productions, Inherit the Wind 1998 (Box-folder 25:34)
  - Clippings, Productions, Violet 1999 (Box-folder 25:35)
  - Clippings, Productions, Three Tall Women 1999 (Box-folder 26:1)
  - Clippings, Productions, Ella and Her Fella, Frank 1999 (Box-folder 26:2)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Sisters Rosensweig 1999 (Box-folder 26:3)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Old Settler 1999 (Box-folder 26:4)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Woman in Black 2000 (Box-folder 26:5)
  - Clippings, Productions, Full Gallop 2000 (Box-folder 26:6)
  - Clippings, Productions, Sweet Charity 2000 (Box-folder 26:7)
  - Clippings, Productions, Side Man 2000 (Box-folder 26:8)
  - Clippings, Productions, Gross Indecency 2000 (Box-folder 26:9)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Carousel 2000 (Box-folder 26:10)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Coming of the Hurricane 2001 (Box-folder 26:11)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Misfits 2001 (Box-folder 26:12)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Taming of the Shrew 2001 (Box-folder 26:13)
  - Clippings, Productions, The 1940's Radio Hour 2002 (Box-folder 26:14)
  - Clippings, Productions, A Little Night Music n.d. (Box-folder 26:15)
  - Clippings, Productions, The Campaign Trail n.d. (Box-folder 26:16)
  - Newsletters, Curtain Up, and Theatre Richmond 1989-1990 (Box-folder 26:17)
  - Newsletters, The Dramatists Guild Quarterly 1994 Winter (Box-folder 26:18)
  - Newsletters, The Dramatists Guild Quarterly 1997 Summer (Box-folder 26:19)
  - Newsletters, The Barksdale Buzz 1992-2001 (Box-folder 26:20)
  - Newsletters, The Orator, Patrick Henry High School 1966 (Box-folder 26:21)
  - Newsletters, National Theatre Critics' Reviews, and New York Theatre Critics' Reviews 1993-1996 (Box 27)
  - Newsletters, London Theatre News 1993-1996 (Box 27)
- Series VI. Production files, 1954-2000., Extent: 3.5 cu. ft. (10 boxes). (Box 28-37)
  The Production files Series is housed in 9 boxes and arranged chronologically with the year in parenthesis indicating the date of the opening. The documentation for each production varies in scope and may include notes, reviews, scripts, directing books, musical scores, press releases, royalty statements, budgets, prop lists, cast contact lists, actors photographs and resumes, costume and set designs, rehearsal schedules, finances, invitations, advertising, memorandum, and correspondence. The later works (from the 1990's) are represented by much more extensive documentation than the earlier productions. The exception being Red, Hot, and Cole (1977), which is extensively documented and includes agreements, audition notes, correspondence, director's notebooks, invitations, reviews, scripts, sheet music, and sketches.
  The earlier shows, 1954-1970, mainly include invitations, notes on ticket sales, play production licenses, and finances. Also included in the earlier records is a collection of correspondence and receipts regarding royalty fees and purchases of copies of plays, 1956-1963. Additional correspondence regarding royalty fees can be found in Series II, Correspondence, General. Of note is a ledger, 1958-1959, recording the attendance and dinner reservations for performances during these years.
  - Gold in the Hills Play production license 1954 (Box-folder 28:1)
  - High Tea Ticket sales 1955 May (Box-folder 28:2)
  - Antigone Ticket sales 1955 June (Box-folder 28:3)
  - Hay Fever Ticket sales 1955 June (Box-folder 28:4)
  - Gold in the Hills Play production license 1955 October (Box-folder 28:5)
  - Typewritten copies of press releases for the 1955 season 1955 (Box-folder 28:6)
  - Handwritten notes on costumes needed for 1956 season 1956 (Box-folder 28:7)
  - Correspondence and receipts regarding royalty fees and charges to purchase copies of plays from Dramatists Play Service, Inc., and Samuel French, Inc. 1956-1960 (Box-folder 28:8)
  - The Little Hut Watercolor drawing of set design by Dorothy Midgette 1958 January (Box-folder 28:9)
  - Laura Box office report 1958 October (Box-folder 28:9a)
  - Arsenic and Old Lace Invitation to play from the Public Relations Association to Stuart B. Hopkins 1958 November (Box-folder 28:10)
  - Where's Charley? Notes on materials received 1959 (Box-folder 28:11)
  - John Brown's Body Director's notebook and script 1961 (Box-folder 28:12)
  - Correspondence and receipts regarding royalty fees and charges to purchase copies of plays from Dramatists Play Service, Inc., and Samuel French, Inc. 1961-1963, 1997 (Box-folder 28:13)
  - Never Too Late Opening night invitation 1965 (Box-folder 28:14)
  - Stop the World Opening night invitation 1966 (Box-folder 28:15)
  - Luv Opening night invitation 1967 (Box-folder 28:16)
  - Annie Get Your Gun Opening night invitation 1969 (Box-folder 28:17)
  - I do, I do Opening night invitation 1970 (Box-folder 28:18)
  - My Fat Friend Sketch of set design by Tim Priddy 1976 (Box-folder 28:19)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole Audition notes 1977-1981 (Box-folder 28:20)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Correspondence 1977 (Box-folder 28:21)
    Correspondence with Muriel McAuley and the Cole Porter Trusts regarding the idea of the play and royalty rights and fees
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Directors notebook, Part 1 of 2 1977 (Box-folder 28:22)
    Includes notes, revisions, and set designs
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Directors notebook, Part 2 of 2 1977 (Box-folder 28:23)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Drawings 1977 (Box-folder 28:24)
    Drawing of actors in play by Mark Longaker, 1977, and advertisement sketch
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Notebook 1977 (Box-folder 28:25)
  - Ledger 1958-1959 (Volume 29)
    Recording reservations and attendance for performances
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Invitations 1977-1984 (Box-folder 30:1)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Notes 1977 (Box-folder 30:2)
    See Oversize Subseries 5 for a sketch of the general floor plan setting for Red, Hot, and Cole, designed by Tim Priddy, 1976
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Script 1977 (Box-folder 30:3)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Script 1977 (Box-folder 30:4)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Script 1977 (Box-folder 30:5)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Script 1977 (Box-folder 30:6)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Script 1977 (Box-folder 30:7)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Script revisions 1977 (Box-folder 30:8)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Script revisions 1977-1988 (Box-folder 30:9)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Script revisions 1977 (Box-folder 31:1)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Script revisions 1977 (Box-folder 31:2)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Script revisions 1977 (Box-folder 31:3)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Script revisions 1977-1988 (Box-folder 31:3a)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Sheet music 1977 (Box-folder 31:4)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Sheet music 1977 (Box-folder 31:5)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole, Traveling show 1979 (Box-folder 31:6)
    Partnership agreement, programs, and reviews for performances in Los Angeles, California
  - Pat Carroll 1980-1982 (Box-folder 31:7)
    Reviews, programs, contracts, and correspondence relating to Pat Carroll's performances in Gertrude Stein, The Merry Wives of Windsor, and Cinderella
  - Gertrude Stein, Gertrude Stein 1982 (Box-folder 31:8)
    Correspondence, advertising costs and receipts, news releases, reviews, stage requirements, and contracts
  - Can We Talk...? Flyer 1984 (Box-folder 32:1)
  - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Raincoat Reviews and partial script 1984 June (Box-folder 32:2)
  - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Raincoat, Traveling show 1986-1987 (Box-folder 32:3)
    Correspondence, advertising costs and receipts, tour schedule, reviews, contracts, invoices, and notes
  - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Raincoat, Traveling show 1986-1987 (Box-folder 32:4)
  - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Raincoat, Traveling show 1986-1987 (Box-folder 32:4a)
  - Stepping Out Cast contact list 1990 (Box-folder 32:4b)
  - Twelfth Night Script, with directors notes 1992 (Box-folder 32:5)
  - Oh dad, Poor dad, Mamma's hung you in the closet and I'm feelin' so sad Cast contact list 1993 (Box-folder 32:5a)
  - Bojangles 1993 (Box-folder 32:6)
    Resumes, performance reports, photograph call schedule, reviews, correspondence, and contact sheet
  - Bojangles Draft of script 1993 (Box-folder 32:7)
  - Bojangles Script 1993 (Box-folder 32:8)
  - Bojangles Script 1993 (Box-folder 32:9)
  - Love letters Cast contact list 1994 April (Box-folder 32:9a)
  - A Day in Hollywood/A Night in the Ukraine Invitation to Champagne Night 1994 June (Box-folder 32:10)
  - Talley's Folly Cast contact list 1994 August (Box-folder 32:10a)
  - The Turn of the Screw Script 1994 August (Box-folder 32:11)
  - The World Goes Round Cast contact list 1994 November (Box-folder 32:11a)
  - Barksdale's Top Forty Gala, 40th Anniversary Celebration Script 1994 (Box-folder 32:12)
  - List of each director, stage manager, musical director, etc. for plays during the year 1995 (Box-folder 32:13)
  - Born Yesterday Cast contact list 1995 (Box-folder 32:13a)
  - Nunsense Agreement and price list for promotional materials 1995 (Box-folder 32:14)
  - Hanover Tavern Haunted Tour Memorandum and script description 1995 (Box-folder 32:15)
  - January, The Search for Signs of Intelligent Life in the Universe 1996 January (Box-folder 32:16)
    Program drafts, press releases, advertising costs and receipts, and reviews
  - The Trip to Bountiful 1996 March (Box-folder 33:1)
    Program drafts, reviews, advertising costs and receipts, correspondence, finances, and schedule
  - Oil City Symphony 1996 May (Box-folder 33:2)
    Program drafts, correspondence, advertising costs and receipts, press releases, and design drawings for new theatre at Willow Lawn (Richmond, Va.)
  - Das Barbecu 1996 July (Box-folder 33:3)
    Program drafts, correspondence, advertising costs and receipts, budget, rehearsal schedules, and reviews
  - The Taffetas 1996 November (Box-folder 33:4)
    Correspondence, programs, advertising costs and receipts, contact sheet, and reviews
  - The Taffetas Script 1996 (Box-folder 33:5)
  - The Taffetas Musical score 1996 (Box-folder 33:6)
  - The House of Blue Leaves 1997 January (Box-folder 33:8)
    Program drafts, advertising costs and receipts, press releases, actors resumes and photographs, contact sheet, and budget
  - The Complete Works of Wllm Shkspr (Abridged) 1997 February (Box-folder 33:9)
    Programs, advertising costs and receipts, press releases, reviews, flyers, directors notes, and prop list
  - The Complete Works of Wllm Shkspr (Abridged) Directors notebook 1997 (Box-folder 33:10)
  - Molly Sweeney 1997 May (Box-folder 34:1)
    Program drafts, advertising costs and receipts, reviews, and rehearsal schedule
  - Molly Sweeney Script 1997 (Box-folder 34:2)
  - Blues in the Night 1997 June (Box-folder 34:3)
    Program drafts, actors resumes and photographs, advertising costs and receipts, reviews, and press releases
  - Love!, Valour!, Compassion! 1997 August (Box-folder 34:4)
    Program drafts, advertising costs and receipts, correspondence, and reviews
  - Love!, Valour!, Compassion! Script 1997 (Box-folder 34:5)
  - The Woman in Black 1997 September (Box-folder 34:6)
    Program drafts, advertising costs and receipts, actors resumes and photographs, and memorandum
  - Red, Hot, and Cole 1997 November (Box-folder 34:7)
    Programs, contact sheets, reviews, advertising costs and receipts, press releases, invitations, and performance schedule
  - From the Mississippi Delta 1998 March (Box-folder 34:8)
    Reviews, program drafts, actors resumes and photographs, schedule, press releases, correspondence, and notes
  - From the Mississippi Delta 1998 March (Box-folder 34:9)
  - The Young Man From Atlanta 1998 April (Box-folder 34:10)
    Programs, reviews, advertising, actors resumes and photographs, press releases, and notes
  - The Young Man From Atlanta Partial script 1998 (Box-folder 35:1)
  - The Rocky Horror Picture Show 1998 May (Box-folder 35:2)
    Press releases, advertising, correspondence, costume drawings
  - Inherit the Wind 1998 September (Box-folder 35:3)
    Advertising, contact sheets, and reviews; see Oversize Subseries 5 for a sketch of the stage setting
  - She Loves Me 1998 November (Box-folder 35:4)
    Cast list, advertising, press releases, reviews, and cast biographical information forms
  - Barksdale Lunchtime Theatre Flyer 1998 (Box-folder 35:5)
  - The Sisters Rosensweig 1999 (Box-folder 35:6)
    Program, press release, and correspondence
  - The Old Settler 1999 February (Box-folder 35:7)
    Program drafts, press releases, show schedule, contact sheets
  - Three Tall Women 1999 (Box-folder 35:8)
    Program drafts, press releases, cast biographical information forms, and advertising
  - J oseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat 1999 (Box-folder 35:9)
    Program, contact sheets, flyers, advertising, schedule, actors photographs and resumes, and reviews
  - Golf with Alan Shepard 1999 (Box-folder 35:10)
    Reviews, correspondence, programs, and advertising
  - Golf with Alan Shepard Script 1999 (Box-folder 35:11)
  - Golf with Alan Shepard Script 1999 (Box-folder 36:1)
  - Violet 1999 (Box-folder 36:2)
    Program drafts, press releases, reviews, budgets, show schedule, and advertising
  - Ella and Her Fella, Frank 1999 November (Box-folder 36:3)
    Reviews, audition forms, correspondence, show schedule, and actors photographs and resumes
  - Ella and Her Fella, Frank Directors notebook 1999 (Box-folder 36:4)
  - Ella and Her Fella, Frank 1999 (Box-folder 36:5)
    Contact sheets, show schedule, partial script, and newsletter
  - Ella and Her Fella, Frank 1999 (Box-folder 36:6)
    Program drafts, newsletters, reviews, and advertising
  - Sweet Charity Program and advertising 2000 (Box-folder 36:7)
  - Sweet Charity Script 2000 (Box-folder 36:8)
  - Sweet Charity Musical score 2000 (Box-folder 37:1)
  - 2000 (Box-folder 37:2)
  - Full Gallop 2000 (Box-folder 37:3)
    Programs, advertising, show schedule, press releases, and budget
  - Side Man 2000 (Box-folder 37:4)
    Programs, reviews, and actors photographs
  - The Queen of Bingo Advertising and partial script 2000 (Box-folder 37:5)
  - Carousel Rehearsal schedule 2000 (Box-folder 37:6)
  - A Tribute to the King Flyers Undated (Box-folder 37:7)